Guide to the Larry LaRocco Collection 1982-1994
Boise State University Library, Special Collections and Archives
- General files, 1
  - Interior Appropriations: Idaho Water Resources, FY95, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    Idaho--Water Resources; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Land and Water Conservation Fund, FY92, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Land and Water Conservation Fund, FY93, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Mackay Bar Ranch; Central Idaho Wilderness Act; Public Land; Hulls Gulch Nature Preserve; Boise, Idaho; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Lucky Dog Ranch, FY95, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Forest Reserves; Nature Conservancy of Idaho; Henry's Fork of the Snake River; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Miscellaneous, FY95, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Snake River Birds of Prey Conservation Area; Wolves; Mountain Lions; National Biological Survey; Hornocker Wildlife Research Institute; Presidio; National Parks; Endangered Species Act; Wildlife--Habitat; Department of Interior
    Hornocker, Maurice
    Statement before Subcommittee on Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: National Endowment for the Arts, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Department of Interior; Grazing Fees; Arts
    Stallings, Richard H.; Helms, Jesse
  - Interior Appropriations: National Endowment for the Arts, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Department of Interior
  - Interior Appropriations: Nez Perce Tribe, FY95, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Inter-tribal Bison Cooperative; Nez Perce Indians; Indians of North America; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Payette Wild and Scenic Rivers Study, F, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Payette River; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Pheasants, FY93, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Wetlands; Pheasants; Idaho Fish and Game; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Projects, FY92, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Painter, Mine; Nez Perce Indians; Bureau of Indian Affairs; Coeur d'Alene Indians; Aryan Nations; Department of Interior Appropriations
    Day, Ernie
  - Interior Appropriations: Projects, FY94, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Nez Perce Indians; Taft Tunnel; Coeur d'Alene Indians; Nez Perce National Historic Park; Mackay Bar; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Raptor Research Grant, FY95, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Boise State University--Raptor Research; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Salmon, FY95, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Northwest Power Planning Council; Salmon; Department of Interior Appropriations
    Bottiger, R. Ted
  - Interior Appropriations: Shoshone Bannocks, FY95, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Columbia River; Water Quality; Fort Hall Indian Reservation; Shoshone-Bannock Indians; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Subcommittee Hearings, FY92, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Salmon; Forest Reserves; Indians of North America; Snake River Birds of Prey National Conservation Area; Timber; Department of Interior Appropriations
    Statement before Subcommittee Interior and Related Agencies
  - Interior Appropriations: Subcommittee Hearing, FY93, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    World Center for Birds of Prey; Peregrine Falcons; Forest Reserves; Fish and Wildlife Service; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Subcommittee Hearing, FY94, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Snake River Birds of Prey Conservation Area; Public Lands; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Taft Tunnel, FY95, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Route of the Hiawatha; Taft Tunnel; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: The Peregrine Fund, FY95, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    World Center for Birds of Prey; Peregrine Falcons; Department of Interior Appropriations
  - Interior Appropriations: Timber Interests, FY95, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    Yates, Sidney
  - International Arts Program, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    International Arts; Arts
  - International Banking, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    Banks and Banking--International Relations; National Treatment in Banking Act
    H.R.4926
  - International Developement: Barney Frank Subcommittee, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    Russia
    Frank, Barney
  - International Development, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - International Development, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    Asian Development Bank; African Development Bank; Banks and Banking
  - International Development, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    Morrison Knudsen; World Bank; Banks and Banking
  - International Development: Barney Frank Subcommittee, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - International Development: Barney Frank Subcommittee, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    Global Ecology; National Wildlife Federation
  - International Development: Barney Frank Subcommittee, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    Global Ecology; North American Development Bank; NAFTA
  - International Development: Barney Frank Subcommittee: Hearing, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    Global Ecology
    Statement on World Bank
  - International Development: Barney Frank Subcommittee; Markup, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - International Exchange Conference: Lewis-Clark State College, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - International Monetary Fund, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    International Development; Banks and Banking
  - International Monetary Fund, 1991-1993 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    International Development; World Bank; Banks and Banking
  - International Monetary Fund, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    International Assistance
  - International Monetary Fund: August 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Freedom Support Act
    H.R.4547
  - International Monetary Fund: External Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - International Monetary Fund: Soviet Aid, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Freedom Support Act; Russia; Export-Import Bank
    H.R.3428
  - International Monetary Fund: Soviet Aid: Bill and Amendments, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - International Pesticide Regulations, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Pesticides; Circle of Poison Prevention Act; Water Quality
    H.R.2083
  - International Trade, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    International Trade; Canada--Wheat; Barley
    Nuzum, Janet A.
  - Interstate Banking, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    H.R.3841
  - Interstate Banking, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Nationwide Banking; Interstate Banking Efficiency Act; Banks and Banking
    Styron, Richard F.; LaWare, John P.
    H.R.459; H.R.2235
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Railroads; Department of Commerce
    Mead, Kenneth M.
  - Investment Adviser H.R.5726, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Agricultural Credit; Investment Advisers Regulatory Enhancement Disclosure Act; Financial Planners; Banks and Banking
    H.R.5726
  - Iran, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Iran/Contra Special Provisions, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Iran-Contra Investigations
    Walsh, Lawrence E.
  - Iraq, 1990-1993 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Persian Gulf War; Economic Sanctions
  - Iraq: Senate Votes, 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    International Relations; Economic Sanctions
  - Iraqi Refugees, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Israel, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Israel, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Economic Aid; Jews--Migration; International Relations
  - Israel, 1991-1993 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    Foreign Relations
  - Israel, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    Middle East
  - Israel: Foreign Aid, 1991-1993 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    Economic Development
  - Israel: Loan Guarantees, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    Economic Aid; Jews--Migration; Middle East
  - Israel: Loan Guarantees, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    Economic Aid; Jews--Migration
  - Japan, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    Trade Expansion Act; International Trade; Persian Gulf War; Tariff
    H.R.5100
  - Japan, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Japanese Potato Tariffs, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    International Trade; Japan--Trade
  - Japanese Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    Japan--Economic Relations
  - Jesse Turner/Lebanon, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Lebanon--Hostages
    Turner, Badr; Turner, Jesse Jon
  - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1991-1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Idaho Theatre for Youth; Arts
  - John Mumma, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Sikorski, Gerry; Craig, Larry
  - Judiciary, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Homosexuality; Civil Rights; Discrimination
    H.R.431
  - Kenneth Sonneck: Background, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Nez Perce Indians; Indians of North America--Legal Affairs; Indians of North America--Land Claims
  - Kenneth Sonneck: Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Kenneth Sonneck: Hattie Davis Rogers, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Nez Perce Indian Tribe; Indians of North America--Legal Affairs; Indians of North America--Land Claims; Native American Rights Fund
    Deer, Ada
    H.R.444
  - Kenneth Sonneck: Hearings, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Rogers, Hattie Davis
  - Kenneth Sonneck: Justice Opinion, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Kenneth Sonneck: Statements, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Kenneth Sonneck: The Bill, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    H.R.5359; H.R.444
  - Kootenai County Task Force on Human Relations, 1981-1991 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    Human Rights; Kootenai County, Idaho
  - Korea, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Kuwait, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    Persian Gulf Veterans National Medal; Silver Medal Act
    P.L.102-281
  - Kuwait Reconstruction, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    Persian Gulf War, 1991
  - Labor Issues, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    Trade Unions; Rural Postal Service; Wage and Hour Reform and Equity Act
    H.R.2710; H.R.4271
  - Land and Water Conservation Fund, 1991-1994 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    Idaho Department of Parks and Recreation; Community Enhancement Act; Land and Water Conservation Fund Act
    H.R.1749
  - Land Exchange, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    Bureau of Land Management; Owyhee County, Idaho; Public Lands
  - Land Exchange, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    Public Lands; Oregon--Forest Reserves; Forest Health
  - Landfills, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    Sanitary Landfills; Municipal Solid Waste Control Act; Twin Falls, Idaho; Bonner County, Idaho; Transportation--Solid Wastes
    Seiber, Roger; Craig, Larry
    H.R.2848; H.R.2926; H.R.4779
  - Latchkey Children, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Latin America, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    School of the Americas; Defense Authorization Act; Human Rights
    H.R.4301
  - Latin America, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    Central America; Chile; Venezuela; Argentina; El Salvador; Human Rights
  - Law Enforcement, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    Idaho--Law Enforcement
  - Legal Services, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Legal Services, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    Pesticides; Migrant Labor
  - Legislative Procedures, 1984-1994 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Lender Liability, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    Solid Waste Disposal Act; Comprehensive Environmental Response, Compensation, and Liability Act; Superfund; Environmental Protection Agency; Banks and Banking
    H.R.2462
  - Leroy Lee, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    Timber Industry; Forest Reserves
  - Lewis and Clark: Bicentennial Expedition, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    Lewis and Clark Trail
  - Lewiston, Idaho, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Lewiston, Idaho: Water Project, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    Lewiston, Idaho--Water Resources
  - Life Insurance/Pensions, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Link Pilot Project, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    Link Project; Environmental Technology
  - Liquid Metal Reactor, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    INEL; Nuclear Reactors; Advanced Liquid Metal Reaction Program; Nuclear Waste--Storage
  - Literacy, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    University of Idaho; Public Libraries; Education
  - Lobbying Reform, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    Lobbying Disclosure Act; Ethics Reform Act
    S.349
  - Log Branding, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    Logging Safety Program; Timber Industry; Log Export Act
    Kludt, David
  - Log Exports: DeFazio's Efforts, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    Exports--Timber
  - Log Exports: General, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Log Exports: Letter to the President, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    Exports--Timber; Logging
  - Log Exports: State Ban, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    Forest Resources Conservation and Shortage Act; Exports--Timber
    H.R.2343
  - Log Exports: Taxes, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    Export Taxation--Timber; Exports--Timber
  - Longer Combination Vehicles (LCV's), 1991 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    Trucking; Idaho--Roads
  - Lower Salmon River: Background, 1990-1993 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    Central Idaho Wilderness Act
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Bills, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    Salmon River; Payette River
    H.R.4083; H.R.4079; S.2101; H.R.233
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Co-sponsors, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    Wild and Scenic Rivers; Niobrara River; Salmon River; Payette River
    H.R.1548; H.R.4079
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    Bureau of Land Management; Powerboats; Friends of the Payette; Hydroelectric Power; Wild and Scenic Rivers; River Guides; Salmon River; Payette River
    H.R.4079; S.2101; H.R.233
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Economics of Payette, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Hydroelectric Power; Salmon River; Payette River
    Walker, Dave
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Gem Irrigation, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Hydroelectric Power; Salmon River; Payette River; Wild and Scenic Rivers
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Hearing, 1992 April 7 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    National Parks and Public Lands Subcommittee; Salmon River; Payette River; Wild and Scenic Rivers; Idaho Rivers United; Fishing Guides
    H.R.4079
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Hearing, 1994 July 19 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Hells Canyon Alliance; Wild and Scenic Rivers Act; Idaho Rivers United
    H.R.233
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Horseshoe Bend, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Dam Development; Horseshoe Bend Hydroelectric Company; Salmon River; Payette River
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Important Correspondence, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Idaho Farm Bureau; Idaho Rivers United; Salmon River; Payette River
    Andrus, Cecil D.; Craig, Larry E.
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Lower Salmon, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Rock Creek; Wild and Scenic River; Salmon River; Payette River
    H.R.4083
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Management Plans, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Maps, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Payette River, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Idaho Rivers United; Wild and Scenic Rivers Act; Clean Water Act; Salmon River
    Crapo, Michael D.; Paul, Liz; Chenoweth, Helen; Strong, Clive J.
    H.R.233; H.R.5021
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Power Boats, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    Wild and Scenic Rivers Act; Salmon River; Payette River
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Press, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Wild and Scenic Rivers Act; Salmon River; Payette River; Hydroelectric Power; Dams
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Statements, Positions, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    Speech to Subcommittee on National Parks, Forests and Public Lands 5-21-1992; Speech to Subcommittee on National Parks, Forests and Public Lands 7-19-1994
    H.R.233; H.R.4083
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Transportation Concern, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    Wild and Scenic Rivers Act; Salmon River; Payette River; Lochsa River; Clearwater River
    Kiebert, Kermit
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Wild and Scenic Rivers Act, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Lower Salmon/Payette River: Withdrawals, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    Public Lands; Salmon River
  - Lumbee Tribe, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    Shoshone-Bannock Indians; Nez Perce Indians; Lumbee Indians; Indians of North America
    H.R.1426
  - Lumber Mills: Environmental Protection Agency, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    H.R.2898
  - Lumber Mills: Environmental Protection Agency; Chlorine, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    Browner, Carol
  - Lumber Mills: Environmental Protection Agency; Dioxin, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Lumber Mills: Environmental Protection Agency; Recycling, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    Recycled Products
  - Lumber Prices, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    Potlatch Corporation; Timber Industry; Canada--Lumber; Lumber
  - Lumber Prices, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    National Association of Home Builders; NAFTA; Forest Reserves; Wilderness Society
  - Lumber Prices, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    Lumber; Housing
  - Lumber Prices, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    Timber Industry
  - Lumber Prices and Housing Affordability, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Habitat for Humanity
  - Managing Northwest Federal Forest Lands, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Ecosystems; Forest Reserves
    Oliver, Chad
  - Marine Mammals Protection Act, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    Ocean Ecology
    H.R.2760
  - Meal Deductibility Tax, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    Tax Deductions; Budget Deficits
  - Merchant Marine: Cargo Preference, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    Agriculture; International Trade; Russia; Merchant; Marine
  - Mexico, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Mexico--Presidential Elections; Human Rights
  - MIA/POW, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    Vietnam; Prisoners of War; Missing In Action
    H.R.291
  - Micron Technology, Inc., 1993 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    South Korea; Computer Technology; Semiconductors
  - Micron Technology, Inc., 1994 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    National Flat-Panel Display Initiative
  - Middle East, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    Israel; Palestine
  - Middle East Peace Talks, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Israel; Saudi Arabia
  - Military Academies, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Military Base Closures, 1991-1993 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Idaho--Military Bases
  - Military Base Closures, 1991-1993 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Idaho--Military Bases; Mountain Home Air Force Base
  - Military Base Closures, 1991-1993 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Idaho--Military Bases; Idaho National Guard
  - Military Land Reform and Reassessment Act, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Bureau of Land Management; Idaho--Military Training Camps; Idaho National Guard
    Statement on "Military Land Reform and Reassessment Act"
    H.R.3564
  - Military Retiree Cola, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Military Retirements
    H.R.3023
  - Military Use of Public Lands, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Military Training Camps--Environmental Aspects
  - Mining, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Mines and Mining
    H.R.322
  - Mining, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Mining, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Mining, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Mining Conference: Bunker Hill, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    Mines and Mining; Natural Resources; Bunker Hill Mine
  - Mining Conference: Bunker Hill, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    Mines and Mining; Bunker Hill Mine
  - Mining Issues, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Mining Law, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Mines and Mining; Mining Law of 1872; Mineral Exploration and Development Act
    H.R. 918
  - Mining Law, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Mines and Mining; Mining Law of 1872
    H.R. 918; H.R.322
  - Mining Law, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Bureau of Land Management; Mines and Mining
  - Mining Law, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Mining Law Changes, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Mining Law Hearing, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    Mineral Exploration and Development Act; Mines and Mining
  - Mining Law Hearing, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    Mines and Mining; Mineral Exploration and Development Act
  - Mining Law Reform, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    Mines and Mining; Natural Resources
    H.R.918
  - Minority Education, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    Higher Education Act of 1965; Minority Education; Education
  - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    Mines and Mining; Super Conducting Super Collider; Helium Mines; Anti-Defamation League
    Richards, Ann
  - Mojave National Preserve, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    California Desert Protection Act; Hunting; Mojave National Preserve Act
  - Military Retiree Cola, 1994 (Box 32)
  - Military Retiree Cola, 1994 (Box 32)
  - Money Laundering, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Drug Traffic
    H.R.3235
  - Money Laundering, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Money Laundering, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Money Laundering Enforcement, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Banks and Banking; Money Laundering Enforcement Amendments of 1991
    Annunzio, Frank
    H.R.26
  - Money Laundering Enforcement: The Bill, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Money Laundering Enforcement Amendments
  - Money Laundering: Efforts to Combat, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Morrison Knudsen, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Morrison Knudsen Corporation; Transportation Systems; Department of Commerce
  - Morrison-Knudsen, 1989-1991 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Railroads; Morrison-Knudsen, Corp.
  - Morrison-Knudsen, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Agency for International Development; Mongolia; Semiconducting Super Collider; International Economics
    Agee, William
  - Mortgage Refinancing Act, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Torres, Esteban E.
    H.R.5170
  - Moscow Mountain, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Moscow Mountain Community Task Force
  - Mountain Home Air Force Base, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Owyhee County, Idaho
  - Mountain Home Air Force Base: Press Coverage, 1991-1993 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Owyhee County, Idaho; Saylor Creek Bombing Range; Grazing; Bombing Ranges--Environmental Aspects
  - Multilateral Development Banks: USSR, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    International Investment; Russia; World Bank
  - Multilateral Development Banks: USSR Human Rights, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Freedom Support Act; Russia
    Baker, James A.
  - Multilateral Development Banks: USSR Human Rights, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Multilateral Development Banks: USSR Human Rights: Department of, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    International Investment; Russia
  - Multipurpose Vehicles Tariffs, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    Automobile Industry--Tariffs
    H.R.4318
  - Municipal Water Projects, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    Idaho--Water Quality
  - Mutual Bank Conversion Act, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    Home Owners Loan Act; Banks and Banking
    H.R.3615
  - NAFTA, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    International Trade; Canada--Trade; Mexico--Trade; Israel--Trade; Global Ecology
    de Gortari, Carlos Salinas, President of Mexico
  - NAFTA, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    International Trade; Department of Commerce
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track", 1991 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    Mexico--Trade; Idaho--International Trade; Hewlett-Packard
    Gephardt, Richard A.; Stallings, Richard; Kolbe, Jim
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track", 1991 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    Immigration; International Trade; Drug Use and Abuse
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track", 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    GATT; International Trade; Idaho--Constituent Communication
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track": Agriculture, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track": Business and Trade Issues, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    GATT; International Trade
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track": Correspondence, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    NAFTA--Constituent Communication
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track": Correspondence, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    NAFTA--Constituent Communication; GATT--Constituent Communication; International Trade
    Statement on floor 05/23/1991
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track": Environmental Aspects, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    GATT; International Trade--Environmental Aspects
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track": Labor, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    GATT; Mexico--Trade; Labor Unions
  - NAFTA: "Fast Track": Opposition, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    NAFTA--Constituent Communication; GATT--Constituent Communication
    Nader, Ralph